To Whom It May Concern,

My name is Magdalena, I am currently based in Buenos Aires (Argentina) after over three years of living abroad.

I have spent a year and nine months in New Zealand studying English at first, and then just gaining some different personal and work experience. I have had the chance to work in various fields: hospitality, farming, manufacturing, customer service, cleaning, etc.

After that time, I went on a trip on my own to explore and travel throughout seven different countries of Southern Asia and, finally, ended up in Australia for another year. When I got there and felt confident enough with the new language and the fact of living in a different culture, my goal had become to get a qualified job position so I strove for it. Unfortunately, by the time I finally got it confirmed (as a Marketing Analyst), my student visa was declined.

About a year ago, I arrived from another trip to India, Nepal and Philippines and, nowadays, I am back in my local city looking for a professional opportunity overseas, since I would like to put my academic and language knowledge in practise, keep gaining expertise, thrive professionally as well as personally and strengthen my inner-force to be able to face any unexpected circumstances in the future.

I have got a Bachelor's degree in Social Communication (with advertising specialization) and have been working in Marketing and Customer Service areas for about four years. Before travelling abroad, I had worked in the Marketing Department at DIRECTV Argentina (a multinational entertainment & television enterprise) as an Online Marketing Analyst for a year and eight months, which prepared me to deal with internal clients and providers. In this job, I was in charge of the email marketing to customers, as well as the mobile campaigns and a bit of the weekly web content update. I also participated in different projects from Latin America to make improvements on the website.

During my time at DIRECTV, not only did we design, plan and execute campaigns for our own needs and strategies, but we also had to attend to internal communication needs from different departments and organize the newsletter, e-mails and text messages depending on priority and relevance. As a consequence of all this, I've learned to work in a demanding and high-pressure environment because of the tight deadlines for each project at the same time.

In addition to that, and before my position at that multinational enterprise, I worked at GrupoPexo agency as an Account Executive, where I coordinated different projects related to online marketing, advertising and some 360° communication campaigns for events for our customers. With regard to the latter, I have also been in charge of some projects specifically related to events' coordination and execution. Nowadays, I perform the position of Office Manager at a credit rating agency.

I consider I have the features required to competently take on such a new challenge. I am an energetic, driven, responsible and flexible person who can work professionally with a multicultural team as well as independently.

I would be available to start working in July, which is when I'm finishing my CELTA. I may be contacted by magdalena.useglio@gmail.com or (+54) 9 11 5743 8270.

Thank you for your time. Yours sincerely,

Magdalena Useglio

Magdalena Useglio

Argentina 24/05/1988

Skype: magdalena.useglio magdalena.useglio@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/magdalenauseglio



KEY SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES

- Language skills
 - English (Advanced. 2005 FCE / 2015 IELTS Band Score 7.5. Intensive English classes in New Zealand General English & Business). CELTA (TEFL qualification).
 - Portuguese (Intermediate level)
 - Spanish (Native)
- Organisational Skills
 - Dynamic / Flexible / Multitasking / Customer Services Skills / Creative
 - Quickly adapt to guidelines and procedures
 - Team Player
 - Cultural awareness
 - Time management
 - Computer Skills (Microsoft Office, Photoshop, After Effects)

ABOUT ME

During the past three years I have been overseas getting a different experience, which has made me become more adaptable and ready for eventual and unexpected changes, besides helping me to develop a quicker reaction when making decisions on a daily basis.

I have also had the chance of backpacking throughout a varied number of Asian and European countries and, consequently, get to know different cultures and ways of living.

EMPLOYMENT

ProRatings

Sept 2017 - Currently

Office Manager: Scheduling meetings and appointments, managing databases, booking transport and accommodation, organizing the office layout and ordering stationery and equipment, maintaining the office condition and arranging necessary repairs, dealing with correspondence, ensuring that all invoices are paid on time and administrating office budget.

Working Holiday Australia

March 2016 - March 2017

I have worked as a Console Operator at BP Petrol Station and as a Kitchen Hand and Catering Assistant.

Student Visa (English) and Working Holiday Visa New Zealand April 2014 – Dec 2015

Different kind of jobs, ranging from Customer Service positions (staff member in MadMex -fast food restaurant-, waitress in Rydges Queenstown Hotel and waitress in CasaBlanca Bar & Grill); seasonal and temporary jobs (tray maker for kiwifruit, cherry sorter and packer, seasonal worker at Hellers -butchery/meat factory-), hospitality jobs (housekeeper and room attendant), and some farming work as well.

DIRECTV Argentina

June 2012 - March 2014

World's leading providers of digital television entertainment services.

■ Mobile and Online Marketing Analyst: SMS and Email Marketing Responsible for Argentina channels, including coordination of different internal areas' needs, strategic and tactical planning of monthly emails and SMS, email marketing campaigns designing, deployment and measurement, reporting results and delivery optimization. I had to liaise with different departments on daily basis and juggle multiple projects simultaneously.

GRUPO PEXO/emBlue

March 2011 - June 2012

Online marketing and advertising agency which had its own email marketing platform developed: emBlue Email Marketing. This business unit was one of the most well-known providers of this service in Argentina.

- Responsible for event coordination: In charge of the whole of two important projects: the Online Marketing Day 2012 and a Telefonica Group's contest for digital entrepreneurs which included technology, marketing and business training sessions throughout different cities in Argentina. Responsible for implementing the online and offline channel strategy (360° communication plan), supervise participants reception and registration, develop meetings and promotion materials, conduct ongoing and post-events evaluations and carry out surveys.
- **Account Manager**: In charge of online campaigns, including search ads, email marketing and social media management. Responsible for following the implementation and development of projects, timing supervision, e-mailing proper delivery and performance improvement.

SMOWTION

Sept 2008 - Aug 2010

AdNetwork company which offers advertising and online services.

■ Account Manager - CRM Representative: In charge of customer care, providing support to owners of blogs and websites (publishers) from all over the world through different communication channels: a messaging platform, a live chat and phone numbers. Responsible for helping with technical issues and payment information.

NEXTEL

July 2008 – Sept 2008

Leading provider of mobile communications for corporate clients.

Customer Service Representative – Call center, support to customers.

EDUCATION

INTERNATIONAL HOUSE BUENOS AIRES

Currently

2014

CELTA (Certificate in Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages)

NTEC NEW ZEALAND

Intensive English Course (14 weeks)

UNIVERSIDAD TORCUATO DIELLA

2013 - 2014

Diploma in Business Management (Incomplete)

UCES (UNIVERSITY OF BUSINESS AND SOCIAL SCIENCES)

April 2006 - Dec 2010

Bachelor in Social Communication with advertisement specialization

UCES (UNIVERSITY OF BUSINESS AND SOCIAL SCIENCES)

2008

News & Broadcasting intensive course

INSTITUTO ARGENTINO DE CEREMONIAL (ARGENTINEAN INSTITUTE OF CEREMONIAL)

Ceremonial & Protocol (2010)

UBA (UNIVERSITY OF BUENOS AIRES)

- Seminar on Event Management (2010)
- Executive Program on Internet Business and Marketing Online (2012)

HOBBIES

- Voleyball / Cycling / Diving / Photography / Writing / Stand-Up Comedy & Acting
- SSI Diving: Advanced Adventurer

* References available upon request